[{"answer": "Well, you know, Obama was 13 points ahead when Hillary Clinton beat him last time, 13 points ahead the night before.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 30, "question": "Are you feeling a little wobbly?", "qSentId": 29}, {"answer": "Well, sure.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "Would you accept that?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 73, "question": "Well, if I was to put you on the spot now and say who are you supporting, have you got a candidate that now got your eye?", "qSentId": 72}, {"answer": "It's what I call the Romney effect.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 97, "question": "Do you think whoever wins the nomination can actually beat Barack Obama, given that the economic climate in America right now appears to be increasing and improving quite markedly?", "qSentId": 96}, {"answer": "We're great.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 119, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 118}, {"answer": "I'm a big fan of baloney.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "Well, we ate a little left baloney growing up, right?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "Well, the great news about our father is he is a life- long learner.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "Has the leopard changed his spots, do you think?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "Everything that's been -- now I'm talking about as a candidate.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 202, "question": "Why do you say that?", "qSentId": 201}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "That's what people in that game do, isn't it?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "No, you rascal, you rascal.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 234, "question": "Is he neutral Mitt?", "qSentId": 233}, {"answer": "Look, he was using it in a totally different context.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "But was it unwise, Jack, in the current climate, with \"Occupy Wall Street\" spreading around America, was he unwise to use a phrase like, \"I like to fire people\"?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "He was talking about -- about his insurance company that are not taking care of him in his health care problems.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "What do you think he meant?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "This is early skirmishes.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "Why isn't he the one they're all getting behind to take on Obama because at the moment they're not?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "I think that one of the -- when I see these ads by Newt Gingrich talking about how people began to lose their jobs when Mitt Romney came to town, it is such a stark contrast from what it was like to actually work at Bain where there was this incredible sort of -- almost bizarre rah-rah, go business, grow business.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 295, "question": "What's the reality behind the myth?", "qSentId": 294}, {"answer": "Never in my experience ruthless.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 301, "question": "Was he ruthless?", "qSentId": 300}, {"answer": "I think we live in a society where you look at him -- I mean it's sort of a weird buys-in (ph).", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "Why hasn't he already got this wrapped up?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "I think it's absolute strength.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "Is it weakness or strength in a leader to do that?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "Is that what you think?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "I don't think so, because they spent it in a different way.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "They are going to have to face that.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "So why should we believe you?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "The problem is we know him more -- as more than a campaigner now.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 387, "question": "And when he gets his gander up, he's a very impressive orator as well, isn't he?", "qSentId": 386}, {"answer": "Well, if his record was so great as governor of Massachusetts, why didn't he run for re- election.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "But can we drop a little bit of the pious baloney?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "It always has been.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "Doesn't it?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "This is what it has all come down to.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "It's so transparent that it actually defeats the whole purpose of saying you can't be involved in these things, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "Part of it.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 447, "question": "Do you agree with that?", "qSentId": 446}, {"answer": "I'd lighten up the regulations.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "If you were president right now, what would you be doing?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "We're back to writing a column again.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "Is this true?", "qSentId": 478}, {"answer": "Jack is the idea generator.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 488, "question": "Who wears the trousers in this column writing gig?", "qSentId": 487}, {"answer": "We have spirited discussions.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "Do you argue?", "qSentId": 493}, {"answer": "My charm and probably my wallet.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "How did you persuade her to marry you?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "We have just really liked each other a ton.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "Suzy, is that heartless assessment true?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "Ten years.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "Was it 10 years?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "That's a question I'll leave to you to answer.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "And should it matter anymore?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "Everybody makes mistake.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "Suzy?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "I'm a guy making movies for 9,000 dollars.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "Which one was it, the charm or the wallet?", "qSentId": 557}, {"answer": "You know, there has been a couple of things that have happened in the last few years.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 563, "question": "How did you go about -- why have you done this?", "qSentId": 562}, {"answer": "I was coming up with the idea for the screen play.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 600, "question": "How did that work?", "qSentId": 599}, {"answer": "Well, the thing that's amazing is using social media now to publicize the film -- we have done this thing where theatrical doesn't make financial sense for indy films, for the most part.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 612, "question": "What do you hope -- what's the expectation?", "qSentId": 611}, {"answer": "Just -- I would say a little shy of that.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 620, "question": "And you have already made what, half a million?", "qSentId": 619}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 662, "question": "Was it in your mind that it might?", "qSentId": 661}, {"answer": "URNS: All the time.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 667, "question": "Do you all hang out together?", "qSentId": 666}, {"answer": "It was at our wedding, yes/", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 673, "question": "It was at your wedding?", "qSentId": 672}, {"answer": "Yes, it is.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 681, "question": "Is being married to Christie Turlington as good as I have always imagined it would be?", "qSentId": 680}, {"answer": "She's waking up next to Ed Burns.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 686, "question": "And she wakes up and looks at me and says, what the hell was I thinking?", "qSentId": 685}, {"answer": "It's not bad.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 690, "question": "Life's pretty good, isn't it?", "qSentId": 689}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 694, "question": "Do you have time?", "qSentId": 693}, {"answer": "You look at all the actors that had the pleasure of working with Payne.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 714, "question": "Wasn't it?", "qSentId": 713}, {"answer": "I will not, no.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 719, "question": "Will you be at the Golden Globes?", "qSentId": 718}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah, yeah.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 721, "question": "So you'll be avoiding the Ricky Gervais roast?", "qSentId": 720}, {"answer": "I just absolutely love it.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 724, "question": "Do you laugh as loudly as I do at the sheer amount of offense he causes?", "qSentId": 723}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "120109pmt", "aSentId": 742, "question": "Could you take it?", "qSentId": 741}]